anal4ever.com 2018-11-22

# Privacy Policy - anal4ever.com - Anal4Ever

PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT WITH GREAT CARE. WHEN YOU SUBSCRIBE AND START USING THIS SITE, YOU WILL EXPRESSLY SIGNIFY THAT YOU AGREE WITH THE POLICIES AND PRACTICES THAT CAN BE FOUND IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT, AS WELL AS THAT YOU ASSENT TO THE USE OF ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT YOU SUPPLY OR THAT IS COLLECTED ABOUT YOU, AS DETAILED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO CERTAIN CLAUSES OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT THEN YOU SHOULD NOT SUBSCRIBE TO OR USE THIS SITE.

The following Privacy Policy Statement contains detailed information when it comes to the use and disclosure of user information and/or data gathered regarding the subscriber (“you”, “subscriber” in the following text) and the website anal4ever.com (“our”, “we”, “us”, “site”, “website” in the following text). In addition to that, this Privacy Policy determines all of the relevant policies and practices for the site.

USE

anal4ever.com is an adult site that expressly and strictly limits its membership to adults. This website does not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons that are under the age of 18. All persons that are under the age of 18, without exception, are strictly prohibited from accessing or viewing content on this website. If you happen to be under the age of 18 or under the legal age in the geographical location where you reside and from which you access this site, your account will be terminated without any notice.

INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM SUBSCRIBERS

Any person that joins/signs up as a subscriber to this website will have to provide personal and demographical information which can include subscriber’s name, physical address, zip code, country, username and password, as well as the e-mail address. This website collects this information and enters it into its customer database. In addition to all of this, other data, such as the IP address(es), referring website information, and other data may be collected, stored and used.

USE OF PERSONAL SUBSCRIBER INFORMATION

If the site decides to feature or conduct any special events, special offers or promotions, polls or contests, a subscriber of the website may be asked to provide information in order to participate. If the subscriber voluntarily provides such information, it may be collected by the site and included into the customer database.

If a personal correspondence of a subscriber is sent to the site, its employees or agents, by any means, the site may collect the information contained within the correspondence and include it in its customer database.

The site may also, albeit automatically, collect traffic and click-through data, as well as the information regarding the online behavior of subscriber by the use of “cookies” or some other programming means. Any information collected in such way will not generally be associated to the specific user.

DISCLAIMER

When the subscriber uses this website, the subscriber expressly agrees that the personal information gathered by the site from the subscriber may be used for an purpose, including without limitation, administrative, technical, research and development, customer administration, age verification, trading of personal data, marketing, promotional and advertising use by the site or third parties that have been authorized by the site to use the information.

By the subscriber’s use of the site, the subscriber expressly agrees that the site may, in its sole discretion, share, transfer, disclose, rent, sell or license any of the personal information gathered or collected with unaffiliated or affiliated third parties.

All of the subscriber’s personal information may be collected by a third-party web service provider that has an advertising link or banner on the website.

The site is not held responsible or liable for the use of any personal information that the subscriber provides, or that has been gathered by a third-party websites that have banner ads or links on the site. The site shall not, in any case, be responsible for the privacy policy or the content of such websites. The site does not monitor, control or endorse the information gathering or collecting practices or privacy policies of mentioned third-party websites.

Whenever it is applicable, the subscriber should seek to read privacy policy of any third-party website that has an advertisement banner, advertises or has a link on the site.

All information collected may be shared if necessary to comply with applicable law and/or cooperate with law enforcement agencies and the tribunals/courts.

In cases of server all technical problems, the subscriber’s IP address may be used to diagnose the named problems. Subscriber’s IP address may also be used to administer the site.

SECURITY OF INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THE SITE

The site has implemented and adopted technologically feasible and reasonable procedures for maintenance of security, integrity and accuracy of all of the subscriber’s personal information that is collected by the site. While the site uses commercially reasonable managerial, technical and physical safeguards to preserve the security and integrity of your personal information, the transmission of information via Internet is not completely safe and secure. All of the information provided to or collected by the website should be considered as non-confidential, and thereby the website does not assume liability or responsibility if any of the subscriber’s information is used and intercepted by an unintended recipient.

FINACIAL INFORMATION

All of the data related to finances will only be shared by the site’s third party processors in order to initiate and complete orders placed on your account. All of the transactions are processed with industry standard encryption through third party processors. Named processors use subscriber’s information solely for the mentioned purpose. All of the data related to finances is considered private information and it shall not be shared by the website with third parties, except with your authorization or when it is necessary to carry out any transaction requested by the user, with the understanding that such transaction could be subject to rules, terms, conditions and policies of the third party in question. Named information and transactions provided to the third party are not governed by this Privacy Policy, and it is a subject to the third party’s terms and conditions.

E-mail address of the subscriber may be used solely for communication when it comes to special offers and other relevant information, such as subscription information, new services, etc. Additionally, there could be a case where the subscriber will receive special offers from administrator or from third-party services or content providers which may contain consent to receive e-mail communications, solicitations, newsletters, commercial advertising, or other special or promotional event materials.

“Opt-in” & “Opt-out” Provisions

OPT-IN AND USER COMMUNICTAION – The subscriber expressly and specifically acknowledges and agrees that this e-mail address or any other means of communication with the subscriber will be used to send him offers, information or any other commercially orientated material. More specifically, some offers may be presented to the subscriber via e-mail campaigns or other means of communication with the option to express the subscriber’s preference by clicking on “yes” or “accept” and “no” or “decline”. By clicking “yes” or “select” the subscriber OPTS-IN to that offer and thereby agrees and assents that his personal information, including e-mail address and data may be used for that matter or disclosed to third parties

.  
OPT-OUT AND USER COMMUNICTAION – The subscriber expressly and specifically acknowledges and agrees that this e-mail address or any other means of communication with the subscriber will be used to send him offers, information or any other commercially orientated material. More specifically, some offers may be presented to the subscriber via e-mail campaigns or other means of communication with a pre-selected choice. If the subscriber does not deselect the pre-selected preference or choice (i.e. OPTS-OUT of the offer), then the site may transfer his personal information and data to the third party. If the subscriber deselects the pre-selected preference, then no personal information or data will be forwarded to the third party.
